<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spoke &amp; Hub</title>
    <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Spoke &amp; Hub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2022 Cube Aim</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/cube-aim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/cube-aim/</guid>
      <description>Whether it&amp;rsquo;s the daily commute or a weekend off-road adventure, the Aim Allroad has got you covered. With a full complement of mudguards, luggage rack, lighting system and kickstand, you&amp;rsquo;re all set for tackling the mean city streets in style and comfort.
Come the weekend, grippy 2.25in tyres, a 100mm Suntour suspension fork and Shimano&amp;rsquo;s wide-ranging 2x8 gears give you the tools you need to explore where your curiosity takes you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikes</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/</guid>
      <description>All Hybrid Black Yellow blue 2022 Cube Aim Allroad Hybrid Bike in Beige
£440.99
Learn more GT Stomper Ace 20 20 Inch Kids Mountain Bike in White
£258.99
Learn more GT Performer 21in Wheel in Black
£279.20
Learn more GT Avalanche 2021 Sports MTB in Blue
£489.99
Learn more GT Zaskar FS Full suspension MTB in Yellow
£279.20
Learn more Roment Grom 65 Romet Grom 65 Silver 20
£250</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cerida Crossway</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/merida-crossway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/merida-crossway/</guid>
      <description>The crossway is the perfect blend of comfort, enjoyment and all around practicality, suitable for leisure rides or commuting.
For ultimate adaptability, the crossway can be equipped with mudguards, racks and kickstands.
Component Specification Frame DT - 6061 double butted technoformed aluminium. BSA BB standard, 135 x 9mm QR axle standard. Mounting points for rack, mudguards and kickstand. Max. tyre size 700 x 42c Fork Suntour NEX; Coil; 63mm travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Address 286 Fox Ln, Leyland PR25 1HJ
Form </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gt Avalanche</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-avalanche/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-avalanche/</guid>
      <description> For the aspiring mountain biker who wants a trusted ride, the Avalanche Elite features an SR Suntour XCT-DS suspension fork, microSHIFT 9-speed shifter, and microSHIFT derailleur, providing a trusted ride that will let their skills develop.
Features: Completely re-designed alloy frame for renewed style and swagger Internal cable routing allows for a clean look New floating seat stays provide additional compliance and comfort Buy Now </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GT Performer</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-performer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-performer/</guid>
      <description>Component Specification Model Name Performer 21 Frame Hi-Ten Steel Tubes, DT Gusset, MID BB , Seat Stay U-Brake, Integrated 1-1/8&amp;quot; H/T w/ Removable Rotor Tabs Fork GT FS Design, Hi-Ten 2pc. Steerer &amp;amp; Tapered Legs, 31mm OffSet, 3/8&amp;quot; Axle Dropouts Rims Alloy Single Wall, 36h Spokes Stainless Steel, 14g Pedals GT Low Profile FS Platform Design Crank GT Power Series Cr-Mo 3pc., 170mm Arms, 19mm x 8T Cr-Mo Spindle, GT 25T Steel Chainwheel Bottom Bracket MID Sealed Bearing Chain KMC Z410 Rear Cogs 9T 1pc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GT Stomper Ace 20</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-stomper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-stomper/</guid>
      <description> Component Specification Frame 20&amp;quot; GT LegitFit Design, Alloy w/ Replaceable Hanger Fork GT Hi-Ten Steel, 1-1/8&amp;quot; Threadless Steerer Rims All Terra Double Wall, 28h Spokes Stainless Steel, 14g Tyres Kenda Small Block Eight, 20 x 2.1&amp;quot; Pedals GT BMX Flat Pedal, Resin Crank Prowheel w/ Double Guard, 30T, 130mm Bottom Bracket Cartridge Sealed Chain KMC Z7, 7-speed Rear Cogs Shimano TZ500, 14-28, 7-speed FW Rear Derailleur Shimano Tourney Shifters Shimano Revo Twist Shifter, SL-RS36, 7-speed Buy Now </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gt Zaskar</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-zaskar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/gt-zaskar/</guid>
      <description> The entry-level, short-travel bike is king of control on punchy climbs and easy-going descents, where suspension and progression go hand-in-hand.
Features: SR Suntour XCR34, 130mm fork SR Suntour Raidon rear shock MicroSHIFT Advent X, 10-speed Buy Now </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Events</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/events/</guid>
      <description>Competitions Fylde Trilogy Ironman Tour of Lancashire Cycle Routes Cycle Routes Cycle Training Active Travel Switch to Cycling Cycling Lancashire Lancashire Cycleway </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Order with Spoke &amp; Hub</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/order/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/order/</guid>
      <description> Select Type: Bespoke Stock Rider Details: Bike Details: Budget: Required By: Select a Bike: Cube Aim Forme Hartington GT Avalanche GT Performer GT Stromer GT Zaskar Merida Crossway Roment Grom Submit </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Team</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/our-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/our-team/</guid>
      <description>Sarah Anderson | Workshop Manager Sarah is the backbone of our service department, ensuring that your bikes receive top-notch care. With over a decade of experience in bicycle maintenance and repair, she is a true master of her craft. Sarah&#39;s meticulous attention to detail ensures that every bike leaving our workshop is in pristine condition. Beyond her technical expertise, she&#39;s an avid mountain biker who loves conquering challenging trails during her free time, making her the perfect leader for our service team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roment Grom 65</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/roment-grom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/roment-grom/</guid>
      <description>The Romet Grom GS Gents Hybrid Bike is a hybrid bicycle that is equipped with reliable, modern components. It is designed for town and country park riding with its sophisticated looks with its comfortable grips and dampened saddle. It is not a bicycle that has been designed for speed, it is a bicycle for those who wish to take a leisurely and relaxed pace (thanks to its 6-speed chain!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romet Grom 6S Silver 20</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/forme-hartington/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/bikes/forme-hartington/</guid>
      <description>For some, a bike is more than just a bike, it is a reflection of ones self.
The Hartington is a functional yet fashionable bike that offers style and sophistication with a splash of fun. With its classic styling and modern geometry, its a bike that doesnt only just look good but also rides as good as many other bikes in other sectors.
Features: Hydro formed alloy frame. Driven by Shimano 21 speed drive train and rolling on 32h alloy wheels and deli tyres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoke &amp; Hub</title>
      <link>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unit6.mansoorbarri.com/about-us/</guid>
      <description>At Spoke &amp;amp; Hub, we are more than just your average cycle shop. We are two brothers, Jake and Ethan, bound by a shared love for cycling and driven by a passion for the open road. With distinct cycling interests, one of us thrives on triathlons, while the other embraces the thrill of road races. Together, we have created a haven for all cycling enthusiasts, a place where our combined knowledge, experience, and love for the sport come together to serve your every cycling need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
